Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Men's and Women's Sports Files, 18.6 cubic ft.
  - Swimming, 0.25 cubic ft.
    - Swimming, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Swimming, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Swimming, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Swimming, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Swimming, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Swimming Time Sheets, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Tennis, 0.5 cubic ft.
    - Tennis, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Tennis, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Athletics, Tennis, Women's, ca. 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Tennis, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Tennis, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Tennis, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Tennis, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Tennis, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Tennis, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Tennis, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Tennis JV and Varsity, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - JV Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - SUNYAC Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Tennis, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Tennis, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Tennis, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Tennis, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Tennis, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Tennis, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Tennis, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Tennis, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Tennis, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Tennis includes history of team from 1963, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - 1989 Men's Tennis, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Men's Tennis, Great Dane Weekly Sports Wrap Up, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Men's Tennis, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Men's Tennis, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Men's Tennis Information, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Men's Tennis Sports Publicity Forms, ca. 1994 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Women's Tennis Eligibility, 1995 January 30 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Women's Tennis Brochure, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Women's Tennis, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Women's Tennis Championships Flyer and Brochure, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - NECC Women's Tennis Tournament, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Women's Tennis, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Women's Tennis Match Notes, 1997; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Women's Tennis, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Women's Tennis, Great Dane Classic Tournament, 1999 April 16-1999 April 18 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Women's Tennis, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Women's Tennis, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Women's Tennis, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Women's Tennis Match Notes, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Women's Tennis Game Notes, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Women's Tennis, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Women's Tennis Championship Program: History, Awards, and Conferences, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Tennis Records, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Tennis, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Women's Tennis Match Programs, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Women's Tennis Ualbany vs. Providence and St Bonaventure, 2007 February (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Women's Tennis, 2009-2011; Undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Intercollegiate Tennis Association Coaches Scorebook, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Women's Tennis, ca. 2015 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Volleyball, 0.42 cubic ft.
    - Volleyball, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Volleyball, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Volleyball, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Women's Volleyball Rosters, 1982; 1984; 1986 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Albany Women's Volleyball Top Ten Statistical Leaders, 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Women's Volleyball, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Volleyball, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - 1994 Volleyball Brochure Information, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - 1992 Volleyball, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Volleyball, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - 1979-1997 Women's Volleyball Records and Statistics, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Volleyball Statistics, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Volleyball, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Volleyball Brochure, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Volleyball, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Volleyball, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Volleyball, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Single-Season Volleyball Records (1983-1999) (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Women's Volleyball Season, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - 2000 Volleyball Season, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - 2002 Volleyball, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - NCAA Women's Volleyball Rules and Interpretations, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Volleyball, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - 2004 Volleyball Player Statistics, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - American Volleyball Coaches Association Division I SID Packet, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - 2005 Season Volleyball (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Volleyball Game Statistics, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Volleyball Records, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Ualbany Volleyball Notes, America East Conference Volleyball Championship, 2006 November 11-2006 November 22 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - NCAA Division I Women's Volleyball Championship, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Volleyball, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Volleyball Profiles and Athletic Questionnaire, ca. 2007-2011 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Volleyball Bios, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Volleyball Athletic Questionnaires, ca. 2017 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Wrestling, 0.38 cubic ft.
    - Wrestling, 1966-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Wrestling, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 2nd E. Stroudsburg Tournament, 1968 November 22-1968 November 23 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Wrestling, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Master Material for Wrestling Notebook, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Wrestling Federation, 1969 April (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Wrestling, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Wrestling, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - SUNYAC Wrestling, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Wrestling, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Wrestling, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Wrestling, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Wrestling, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wrestling, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - SUNYAC Wrestling, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wrestling, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wrestling, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - SUNYAC Wrestling, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Wrestling, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Wrestling, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Wrestling, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Section II HS Coaches' list, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Basketball Administrative Files, 4.83 cubic ft.
  These records are most useful for finding basketball game statistics and team statistics and notes for men's and women's basketball games played from 1989 to 2012. The detailed files were originally organized in binders by the Department of Athletics according to men's and women's team basketball seasons, and cover the ins and outs of each season. The files for each year provide an in-depth look at the players and their schedules. Files may contain rosters, statistics, schedules, results, game notes, player highs and lows, box scores, team histories, tournament information, charts, media and press, articles, travel itineraries, contact information, forms, emails, event notices, contracts, correspondence with Sports Information Director Brian DePasquale and more. In some instances, personally identifiable information and/or sensitive material was redacted to protect the security of individuals mentioned.
  The files are arranged by date of content listed in the title field, not by creation date. Within each athletic year, the files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Women's Basketball: Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Women Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Season (1 of 3), 1994-1995; 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Season (2 of 3), 1994-1995; 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Season (3 of 3), 1994-1995; 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1999-2000 Men's Basketball Season (1 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1999-2000 Men's Basketball Season (2 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball, NCAA Leaders; Independent Conference Releases, RPI Ratings, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2000-2001 Men's Basketball Season (1 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2000-2001 Men's Basketball Season (2 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 2000-2001 Men's Basketball Season (3 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2001-2002 Men's Basketball Season: Team History, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball: America East, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball: Box Scores, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball: Travel, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball (3 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball (3 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball (4 of 4), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball (3 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 4), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 4), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball (3 of 4), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball (4 of 4), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball (3 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball (1 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball (2 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball (3 of 3), 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 2005-2006 Men's Basketball Season (1 of 3), 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 2005-2006 Men's Basketball Season (2 of 3), 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 2005-2006 Men's Basketball Season (3 of 3), 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, Events and Correspondence with Sports Information Directors, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball :America East, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball: Game Notes, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball: Roster Play by Plays, Box scores, and Statistics, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball: Scorebooks/Game Analyses(for years 2000-2005) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball: Season Scorebook/ Game Analyses, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 2006-2007 Men's Basketball: Sports Media and Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 2006-2007 Men's Basketball Season: Tournament Itineraries (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball: America Feast Conference, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball: Box Scores, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes and Articles (1 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes and Articles (2 of2), 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics (1 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics (2 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball (1 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball (2 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball (3 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics (1 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics (2 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2009-2010 Men's Basketball: Box Scores/ Games, 2001-2010 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2009-2010 Men's Basketball: Roster, ca. 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2009-2010 Men's Basketball: Statistics (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes (1 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes (2 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball, Roster, Play-by-Plays, Box Scores, Statistics (1 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball, Roster, Play-by-Plays, Box Scores, Statistics (2 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 2010-2011 Men's Basketball: Box Scores and Statistics (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 2010-2011 Men's Basketball: Game Notes (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 2010-2011 Men's Basketball: Game Notes (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2010-2011 Men's Basketball: Travel Itinerary and America East Championship (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2011-2012 Men's Basketball Season: Athletics Telephone Directory, 2008 September 10 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2011-2012 Men's Basketball Season: Box Scores (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Notes, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2011-2012 Men's Basketball: Game Statistics, 2000; 2008-2011 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2011-2012 Men's Basketball: National Invitation Tournament (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball: Play by Plays and Box Scores, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Football Administrative Files, 2.5 cubic ft.
  These records are most useful for finding football game and team statistics and notes for the football seasons of 1994 to 2010. These detailed files were originally organized in binders by the Department of Athletics and Recreation in summary for each season, and are a good resource for finding specific game information. Files contain rosters, statistics, schedules, scoring summaries, game notes, charts, media and press, articles, travel itineraries, contact information, football training camp papers, forms, emails, event notices, football news, and more for each season. Eastern College Athletic Conference Sports News, Don Hansen's National Weekly Football Gazette, and Northeast Conference press releases are featured. Correspondence with Sports Information Director Brian DePasquale is included. In some instances, personally identifiable information and/or sensitive material was redacted to protect the security of individuals mentioned.
  - 1994 Football (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1995 Football (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1995 Football (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1995 Football (2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1996 Football, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1996 Football: Eastern College Athletic Conference (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1996 Football: Game Summaries (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1996 Football: Media (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1996 Football: Releases (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1997 Football (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1997 Football (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1998 Football: College Sports News Conferences, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1998 Football: Game Notes and Articles (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1998 Football: Game Summaries, Statistics, Articles, Rosters (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1998 Football: Roster, Practice Dates, All Conference Teams, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1999 Football: Game Notes, Articles, and Itineraries (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1999 Football: Northeast Conference, College Sports News, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1999 Football: Roster, Contact Information, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1999 Football: Scoring Summaries, Statistics, and Intineraries (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2000 Football (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2000 Football (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2001 Football (1 of 3), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 2001 Football (2 of 3), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2001 Football (3 of 3), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2002 Football (1 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 2002 Football (2 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2002 Football (3 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 2003 Football (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Football: All- Star Players and Teams (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Football: Game Notes, Statistics, and Articles (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Football: Game Summaries (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Football: Northeast Conference (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Footbll: Preseason (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Football (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2004 Football (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 2004 Football (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2005 Football (1 of 3), 1991-1994; 2002; 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2005 Football (2 of 3), 1991-1994; 2002; 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2005 Football (3 of 3), 1991-1994; 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2006 Football (1 of 3), 2004; 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2006 Football (2 of 3), 2004; 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 2006 Football (3 of 3), 2004; 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 2007 Football: Albany Roster, All America Squad, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2007 Football: Contatct Lists (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 2007 Football: Northeast Conference (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 2007 Football: Schedules/Forms (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 2007 Football: Sports News, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 2007 Football: Statistics Game Summaries, Itineraries (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 2008 Football (1 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 2008 Football(2 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 2008 Football (3 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 2009 Football (1 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2009 Football (2 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 2009 Football (3 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2010 Football (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 2010 Football (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 2010 Football: Northeast Conferrence Game Management Guide (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Score Histories, 0.66 cubic ft.
  This series contains note cards that recorded men's game scores and the history of results with opponent schools for various sports from 1913-1981 (non-inclusive).
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Baseball Opponents and Seasons, 1958-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Basketball Opponents, 1915-1943; 1946-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Basketball Years, 1913-1943; 1946-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cross County Opponents, 1962-1976; 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cross County Opponents and Seasons, 1962-1973; 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cross County Seasons, 1955-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football Opponents and Seasons, 1922-1924; 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lacrosse Opponents, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lacrosse Opponents and Seasons, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lacrosse Seasons, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Soccer Opponents, 1950-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Soccer Opponents and Seasons, 1950-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Soccer Seasons, 1950-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Swimming Opponents, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Swimming Opponents and Seasons, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Swimming Seasons, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tennis Opponents, 1959; 1962-1976; 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tennis Seasons, 1959-1960; 1962-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Track Opponents, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Track Opponents and Seasons, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Track Seasons, 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Volleyball Seasons, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Wrestling Opponents, 1955-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Wrestling Opponents and Seasons, 1955-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Press Releases, 1994 May - 2008 August; 2.33 cubic ft.
  The files are arranged chronologically by month and year of release.
  This series contains sports news releases issued by the University at Albany Department of Athletics and Recreation as well as press releases from sources like the Football Gazette, Metro Atlantic Athletic Conference, New England Collegiate Conference and more that were retained by the Athletics Department.
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 July (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 August (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 September (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 October (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sports News Releases, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 January (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 April (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 July (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 October (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 November (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sports News Releases, 1995 December (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 February (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 March (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 April (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 July (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 July (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 August (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 August (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 September (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 September (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 October (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 October (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 November (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 November (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1996 December (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Sports News Releases, 1996 December (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1997 January (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sports News Releases, 1997 January (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - New England Collegiate Conference Releases, 1997 February (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sports News Releases, 1997 February (Box 1, Folder 42)